westgateresorts.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - Westgate Resorts | Westgate Resorts

Westgate Resorts has a strong commitment to providing excellent service to all of our customers and visitors of our Web sites, including respecting your concerns about privacy. We understand that you may have questions about how we collect and use the information that you provide to us. We have prepared this statement to inform you of the privacy principles that govern our use of information we obtain from our customers, including information we obtain through this Web site and other Westgate sites - [https://westgateresorts.com](https://westgateresorts.com/), [https://my.westgateresorts.com](https://my.westgateresorts.com/), [https://reservations.westgateresorts.com](https://reservations.westgateresorts.com/), [http://westgateowners.com](http://westgateowners.com/) \- which are included in this privacy policy ("Statement").

This Statement contains numerous general and technical details about the steps we take to respect your privacy concerns. We have organized the Statement by major processes and areas so that you can review the information of most interest to you.

At Westgate, meeting your needs and expectations form the foundation of everything we do--including protecting your privacy.

If, after reviewing this Statement, you have any questions or privacy concerns please send a letter to:

Westgate Resorts

Privacy Policy

2801 Old Winter Garden Road

Ocoee, FL 34761-2965

This Statement was last updated on December 31, 2013, to describe how the privacy statement applies to all of the information we obtain from you and to update the privacy statement with respect to Westgate's Authorized Licensees, franchisees and certain other commercial partners set out below.

## Browsing

This Web site does not collect personally identifiable information when you browse this Web site and request pages from our servers unless you provide it to us. This means that we will not know your name, your email address, or any other personally identifiable information just because you browse the Web site unless you:

  * access the Web site from a link in an email that we sent;

  * have input your personally identifiable information via your owner account management login;

  * are a Westgate Rewards member or have created a profile and you either log-in to your account or choose to be remembered via your cookie, including on your web-enabled mobile device; or

  * have input your personally identifiable information via a section of our Web site in which you are requesting to be contacted by Westgate.

In these cases we will know who you are based on the information you previously supplied to us. When you request a page from our Web site, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request and other information that is provided in the HTTP header. We collect the HTTP request header information in order to make our Web sites function correctly and provide you the functionality that you see on this Web site. We also use this information to personalize content presented to you, better understand how visitors use our Web site and how we can better tune it, its contents, and functionality to meet your needs.

## Information We Collect and How it is Used

When we need to collect personally identifiable information from you to provide you with a particular service, we will ask you to voluntarily supply us with the information we need. For example, if you would like to make a reservation at one of our properties, we will ask you for information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card number, and room preference to process your reservation. We will use your email address to send a confirmation and, if necessary, might use the other information to contact you for help in processing the reservation. We will also use your contact information to:

  * send you a non-marketing informational pre-arrival message summarizing your confirmation details and providing other information about the area and the hotel;

  * notify you about special offers and promotions as described in this privacy statement; as well as

  * send you periodic satisfaction or market research surveys.

You can opt out of marketing communications at any time. On occasion, we use third parties to provide us with additional contact information about you given the information you provided to us directly. For example, if we know your name and postal address, we may use a third party to provide us with your email address. We would then use this information for market analysis and marketing purposes.

## Your California Privacy Policy

As a California resident you have the legal right to request from businesses with whom you have an established business relationship, (1) a list of the categories of personal information, such as your name, address, email address and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties.

To request the above information, please mail your written request to the following address, with a reference to California Disclosure Information:

Westgate Resorts

Privacy Policy

2801 Old Winter Garden Road

Ocoee, FL 34761-2965

## Children's Privacy

This Web site is not intended for children and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information from children. We may present information regarding Westgate programs that are for kids on this site for the reference of adults that are interested in activities at our locations for children.

## Reservations

The personally identifiable information you provide to us for making a reservation is made available to the applicable property for the purpose of meeting your reservation request. After making a reservation or completing your stay at a Westgate property, unless you tell us otherwise, the information you provide may be used by us and our Authorized Licensees for marketing of Westgate properties and certain other Westgate branded products. Westgate may use the services of third-party mail houses for the sole purpose of mailing materials.

After your stay we retain your personally identifiable information including details of your stay, room type and accommodation type.

## Accessing our Web site from a Mobile Device

You can access our website from a web-enabled mobile device to find a property (including clicking to call the hotel) or view a reservation. If you desire to view a reservation you will be required to enter your Westgate account user name and password, or Westgate confirmation number and zip/postal code or country. No other personally identifiable information will be requested. In addition, you can make a reservation from a web-enabled device. When you make a reservation you will need to provide certain personally identifiable information such as name, email address and credit card information. Additionally, you can make payments to Westgate, via credit card, by accessing our website from a web-enabled mobile device. To review the security measures Westgate has in place regarding your credit card data, please review the section below titled Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information ASAS.

## Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information

We treat the information you provide to us as confidential information; it is, accordingly, subject to our company's security procedures and policies regarding protection and use of confidential information. When we ask you for credit card data, it is transferred over a Secured Sockets Layer (SSL) line, provided you are using a SSL enabled browser such as Microsoft Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox. We also use SSL on other pages where you would enter personally identifiable information. This ensures that your information is encrypted as it travels over the Internet. This secure mode is enabled before any such information is transmitted from your computer or web-enabled device. You will know you are in secure mode when the padlock or key icon in the lower right-hand or left-hand corner of the computer screen appears in the locked position. In addition, when accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https."

After information reaches us, it is stored on a secure server that resides behind firewalls designed to block unauthorized access from outside of Westgate. Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, our properties or other business operations may put in place additional measures that vary depending on the applicable legal requirements. Information collected on the Web sites covered by this privacy statement is generally processed and stored in the United States.

We typically maintain records for a minimum of five (5) years. In conforming with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you have the option to receive a copy of the information we maintain. Please send a request to Westgate Resorts Owner Relations Department, 2801 Old Winter Garden Rd, Ocoee FL 34761.

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

Westgate may use the services of third party processors, such as market researchers, fulfillment houses, email service providers and mail houses that process mail for Westgate, Westgate's Authorized Licensees, persons authorized by you, as well as such entities and marketing companies that provide these services for Westgate, and Westgate's Authorized Licensees. These parties are contractually prohibited from using personally identifiable information for any purpose other than for the purpose Westgate specifies. We may provide non-personally identifiable information to certain service providers for their use on an aggregated basis for the purpose of performing their contractual obligations to us.

Westgate does not permit the sale or transfer of personally identifiable information to entities outside of the Westgate family of companies, and properties and our third party service providers for any non-Westgate use without your approval.

If you would like to request a list of our third party service providers, please send a letter to:

Westgate Resorts

Privacy Policy

2801 Old Winter Garden Road

Ocoee, FL 34761-2965

## Your Choices/Opt-out

We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes not essential to Westgate's providing services to you, when we ask for this information. You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. If you no longer wish to receive promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing or calling us per the information contained on our contact page.

By providing information to Westgate you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of such personal information in the manner described in this Statement. We provide you the opportunity to withdraw your consent at any time by following the procedure described in this Choice/Opt-Out provision.

Such consent may be withdrawn in writing and sent to our customer service department at the following physical address:

Westgate Resorts

Privacy Policy

2801 Old Winter Garden Road

Ocoee, FL 34761-2965

## Cookies

Our Website uses "cookie" technology. "Cookies" are encrypted strings of text that a Web site stores on a user's computer. Our Web site requires the use of a Cookie throughout the online reservation process. Without Cookies we will not be able to keep information you enter on multiple pages together. Cookies also enable us to customize our Web site and offerings to your needs and provide you with a better online experience. In addition, Cookies are used to:

Measure usage of various pages on our Web site to help us make our information more pertinent to your needs and easy for you to access; and

Provide functionality such as online reservations and other functionality that we believe would be of interest and value to you.

The types of Cookies that we use are referred to as "session" Cookies and "persistent" Cookies. Session Cookies are temporary and are automatically deleted once you close your internet browser. Persistent Cookies remain on your computer hard drive until you delete them or are otherwise removed upon expiration. We do not use Cookies to ascertain any personally identifiable information about you apart from what you voluntarily provide us in your dealings with us. Cookies do not corrupt or damage your computer, programs, or computer files.

## Emails about Special Offers and Promotions and Opt-Out

It is our intention that you should only receive email communications that will be useful to you and that you want to receive. When you communicate with Westgate via email and provide your email address, we may periodically contact you via email and provide information about Westgate special offers and promotions that may be of interest to you (unless you opt out). We may also give you the opportunity to receive Offers and Promotions from Westgate and, its Affiliates concerning other Westgate branded offers and promotions that we believe would be of interest to you.

We typically use third party email service providers to send emails. These service providers are contractually prohibited from using your email address for any purpose other than to send Westgate related email.

Each time you receive an email, you will be provided the choice to opt-out of future emails by following the instructions provided in the email. Please allow 10 business days for us to process your opt-out.

## Other Websites

Westgate is only responsible for the privacy statement and content of this Web site and information we collect. We are not responsible for the data collection and use practices and privacy policy or the use of cookies on Web sites that you have accessed this Web site from and to the non- Westgate Web sites that you may access from this Web site.

## Legal

This is a United States Web site and is subject to laws of the United States and the State of Florida. Westgate will disclose personally identifiable information without your permission when required by law, or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful activities to Westgate guests, visitors, associates, or property (including this site), or to others. As mentioned previously, laws related to personally identifiable information vary by country.

## Other Westgate Resorts Sites accessible from WestgateResorts.com

Within Westgate Resorts are numerous other Westgate Web sites that are accessible from links within WestgateResorts.com or via separate URLs. Namely, these Web sites are:

  * https://my.westgateresorts.com

  * https://reservations.westgateresorts.com

  * https://oam.westgateresorts.com/oam

  * https://rewards.westgatespace.com

  * http://westgatetelesales.com

  * http://westgatedestinations.com

  * http://westgatereservations.com

  * http://westgateevents.com

  * westgatelasvegas.com
